- Welcome!
Welcome
- All right. You can come out now.
- Okay.
Sorry about that.
POURING OUT
They're also guests.
Our boss will give an introduction.
Do it like a docent.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
I'm the owner of Kian's B&B, Kian84.
And they're our employees.
- Yeon-koung.
- Hello.
- Kazuha.
- And finally, Jun-ho.
- Hello.
How are you?
- This is awesome.
And…
BRAIN RESETS
First of all…
Go ahead.
We should show them the facilities
you worked really hard to prepare.
- Like what?
- They're all here, so… Like what?
Facilities?
WE SHOULD SHOW THEM AROUND
Sorry, Jun-ho.
- It's okay.
- I spent a lot of energy earlier.
THEY FOLLOW THE DOCENT
THIS PLACE IS…
It's so efficient.
LAUNDRY ROOM?
We're actually drying
the laundry right now.
- It's a sauna.
- It's really nice.
It's warm.
And let me explain one more thing.
And this place is for you
to manage your health.
It's a gym.
And this TV is…
Could you all gather in front?
Please come to the front of the TV.
KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
Hey, it's a karaoke room.
Nice.
BRAVO
- That's so cool.
- Everyone.
If each of you doesn't sing
at least one song before you check out,
you can't check out.
- Yes. Got it?
- Yes.
THE DOCENT FINISHES SHOWING THEM AROUND
Now, the rooms.
Which one did you choose?
Up there.
THEY CHOSE THE WINDOWSILL
- What about you?
- We'll go here.
THEY CHOSE THE TV CABINET
Good.
Let's sleep in the fridge.
It'll be easier for us to climb up.
- All three of you?
- Yes.
THEY CHOSE THE FRIDGE
Now, we'll have
a comforter presentation ceremony.
Rather than a presentation ceremony,
you have to take them yourselves.
But they're so big.
- Can we just climb up?
- Yes, that's fine.
Do as you please.
You can get on each other's shoulders.
THEY CLIMB UP
SO EASILY
- What do you need?
- Which one…
- The yellow one, please.
- Okay.
Thank you.
It's so heavy.
You're right.
THEY CAN EVEN ORGANIZE THE HANGERS
Is it supposed to be that easy?
- What on earth?
- They're so good.
CURIOUS ABOUT WHO THEY ARE
They must have great core strength.
- Do you do rock climbing?
- Yes.
- You're climbers.
- Climbing.
We do ice climbing.
We're professional ice climbers.
- Complete!
- Descending.
NATIONAL TEAM, KIM MIN-CHEOL
NATIONAL TEAM, PARK JOON-KYU
NATIONAL TEAM, LEE YOUNG-GEON
- You're athletes?
- Yes.
- Their forearms are huge.
- Right.
- You're right.
- Look at their forearms.
We'd been in a competition
up until yesterday.
- National Sports Festival?
- Yes.
Different from the winter one?
A WINTER SPORT LIKE LUGE
- Is it the same as the others?
- Yes.
We had the luge team stay with us before.
So how did it go?
First, second, and third place.
- In the individual event?
- Amazing.
First, second, and third?
We'll prepare dinner now.
- Zuha, will it take long?
- Yes, if I'm starting now.
What do we do?
Boss will help.
- You're going to help me, right?
- Yeah.
JUN-HO GOES TO HELP TOO
- I don't think I can climb this anymore.
- Right?
Seriously, I can't.
- It exhausts your arms, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Why is the volleyball here?
That ball? It bounced up here.
TRACE OF DAZZLING VOLLEYBALL PERFORMANCE
- Could you take this, please?
- Sure.
It's wet.
Here are the wet wipes.
YEON-KOUNG IS HELPING GUESTS
I think I've seen you before.
- Me?
- Yes. No?
No.
Physical: 100.
That's why you looked familiar.
I thought I'd seen you
at the National Training Center.
We haven't been able to train there yet.
- Why not?
- It's not an official Olympic sport.
- Really?
- Yes.
Now, I'm starting to feel a bit hungry.
Are you hungry?
We have a few snacks here.
Sweet potatoes too.
THEY'RE ALL HUNGRY
Zuha, how long will it take?
An hour and a half?
Then, assume it'll take two hours.
What? That's too long.
We'll try an hour and a half then.
They said they're hungry.
What do we do?
- We have to make Hamburg steak.
- Hamburg steak.
- And Napolitan.
- Right, Napolitan.
These go in the Hamburg steak.
Then, should I mince them finely?
Thin like what is used in pasta.
- Cut the bell peppers thinly too?
- Yes.
IN CHARGE OF HAMBURG STEAK INGREDIENTS
KNIFE SKILLS LIKE NANTA
IN CHARGE OF NAPOLITAN INGREDIENTS
WITH A FRUIT KNIFE
DELICATELY AS IF SCULPTING
Zuha, is this good enough?
- My eyes are burning.
- Yes.
I'm sure I can do this.
BREAD CRUMBS
MILK
PORK
BEEF
ONIONS
THE HAMBURG STEAK MIX IS READY
5:30 P.M.
Do you need help up there?
Up here?
Is it going to take a while?
A little bit.
- They said they were really hungry.
- Oh, no.
Cut that one, and it should be enough.
- Stop here? Okay.
- Yes.
- You feel rushed, don't you?
I mean, we always started cooking
before the guests arrived.
Right.
It's hard because we started
after they all came.
Right?
I think you can start at 4:00 p.m.
FAST
You're julienning better
than you did yesterday.
I realized how to do it.
We're getting better.
Right.
- And these things are all new to us.
- Yeah.
- Isn't it a bit stuffy?
Gosh, it's so heavy.
Wait. I can't get down if it's open.
The distance becomes much greater.
Hey, this is way too open.
TOO OPEN
This spot has a great view.
Come up here. The view's nice.
I wonder what else there is.
Nice view.
IT HAS A GREAT VIEW
I'm Kim Jun-yeop.
And I'm Lee In-beom.
THEY INTRODUCE THEMSELVES
- What are your names?
- Should we go over there too?
- This spot is a bit…
- We'll come down.
THEY'RE ALL GATHERED
I am Ground…
SEATING ARRANGEMENT
CALLS FOR PARTY GAMES
- This way!
COMPELLED TO START
I'm Park Joon-kyu.
I'm Kim Jun-yeop.
- I'm Lee In-beom.
- This is too much.
The two of us are a bit older, so…
LEARNING NAMES OVER FOR REAL
LEE IN-BEOM, KIM JUN-YEOP
PARK JOON-KYU
LEE YOUNG-GEON, KIM MIN-CHEOL
CHOI A-RIN, CHOI A-JIN
Siblings?
- Sisters.
- Right.
Siblings? Who is the brother?
Kian, look over there.
Look at them.
- My goodness.
- They're all together.
- This is a first.
- It is.
It's what you wanted.
That's what I drew in my initial plans.
They must be introducing themselves.
They're behaving as we planned
because we welcomed them properly.
- Yeah.
- They don't feel awkward.
I bet they don't.
A warm welcome makes a huge impact.
- We did it three times.
- Yeah, I think it's good.
Are the girls college students?
They resemble each other.
- They're sisters. Yeah.
- Right?
- I wonder what job the ponytail guy has.
I bet there's a story behind it.
- A story?
Maybe he donates it?
- His hair?
- By cutting it?
THEY SUDDENLY BEGIN GUESSING
Well, I was thinking
he might be in a rock band.
A ROCKER?
Rock band guys these days
don't have long hair.
He doesn't seem like one though.
To me, he seems like
someone who does mind-body practice.
A successor to his master's practice.
You sure do have a lot of unique thoughts.
TOO BUSY TO LISTEN
Could you shape the patties for me?
- Make them round? Okay.
- The Hamburg steak.
- We should make them small.
- Let's do that.
- Like mini patties.
- Yes, mini.
- Round like this?
- Yes.
How is this?
You look pretty cool.
While you do that,
we'll hurry up and cook them.
Like this?
Yes.
We can cook them a bit more.
They look so good.
I mean, Zuha's food is the best.
It always has been.
Yeah, her food is always good.
I haven't done this very often.
SHE STARTS MAKING THE NAPOLITAN
Did I put in too many ingredients?
THE PAN IS ALREADY FULL WITHOUT THE PASTA
You have to control portion sizes
to look like a good cook.
If you don't,
you look like a bad cook.
A lot of cow feed
was left over yesterday.
Geez, that's making me mad.
There was more left over than my pizza.
YEON-KOUNG'S LEFTOVER FOOD
I'm taking some consolation from that.
Gosh, I'm so angry.
Don't worry. I'll eat it all.
Yeah, I will too.
Except for Boss's.
Don't worry.
The pasta will be done
sooner than expected.
It's hot!
ADDING KETCHUP
Hold on. It takes a lot of ketchup.
A LOT OF KETCHUP
- Zuha.
- That looks good.
- Yes?
- I think they'll love this.
Yay.
- You'll become the cooking goddess.
- Exactly.
THE COOKING GODDESS'S FINAL TOUCH
Is that right?
Was that on purpose?
Let's just say it's right.
But a lot does go in.
- Really?
- So it should be all right.
Those cooked really well.
- Are these all right?
- They look good.
Jun-ho cooks well.
He didn't burn any of his pizzas either.
- Is this what you envisioned?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- They look so good.
- Should we bring these down?
- Sure.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
TIME TO BRING THE FOOD DOWN
Could you help us with this?
Sure.
Thank you.
We'll get ready to eat now.
TRAYS BROUGHT DOWN FIRST
- I got it. You got the other end?
- Okay.
Gosh, it looks so good.
It's hot. Be careful.
Hamburg steaks!
JUN-HO & THE BOSS COME DOWN TO EAT TOO
AND TODAY'S CHEF ZUHA TOO
This looks amazing.
HAMBURG STEAK & NAPOLITAN
Zuha cooked these.
Could you tell us about your dishes?
I made Napolitan and some Hamburg steaks.
I started ballet
when I was three years old.
And I went abroad to learn it.
Where did you go?
I went to the Netherlands.
ZUHA STUDIED BALLET IN THE NETHERLANDS
So you ate these dishes often there.
Yes, we made these often back then,
so I wanted to introduce them to you.
- Thank you!
And everyone, one more thing…
Before you start to eat,
if you could choose
an employee you'd like to eat with…
EXCITED, FEELING PRESSURE
You can eat and chat with that employee.
We'll get to know each other
faster that way too.
And we'll all get together later
after dinner anyway.
So, please choose the employee
you'd like to eat with.
No pressure.
All right?
- Okay.
Should we turn around? Or…
- Should we do that?
- Let's turn around.
Let's make it quick.
The pasta will get mushy.
I don't think anyone will pick me.
I've never been picked before, so…
We were so torn.
No, it's really all right.
FIRST TIME, 0 VOTES
Two, three.
SECOND TIME, 0 VOTES
You're so popular on social media,
but not so much here.
I guess it's not meant to be.
I don't mind eating alone.
Don't be like that.
I'm so sad. I don't hear anything.
THEY'RE ALL WORRIED
I don't hear any footsteps.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
Then, we'll turn around now.
- One, two, three.
JUN-HO, ZUHA, YEON-KOUNG, KIAN
Thank you!
What a relief!
What is this?
Why did you choose me?
IN-BEOM AND JUN-YEOP PICK JUN-HO
Thank you.
A-JIN AND A-RIN PICK ZUHA
You won't regret it.
MIN-CHEOL PICKS YEON-KOUNG
I'll take good care of you.
YOUNG-GEON AND JOON-KYU PICK KIAN
It looks delicious.
You can just serve yourselves.
No, I'm going to do it for my friends.
SWOONS
What's with you?
- They picked me.
- Nice service.
This is my first time.
It's the first time I've ever been chosen.
Use your own chopsticks
to plate your food.
Where should we eat?
THE BOSS DOESN'T KNOW WHERE TO GO
Finding a place to eat's an ordeal too.
HE SUDDENLY CLIMBS UP THE SOFA
Yeah, I wanted to look
at this while eating.
What a great view.
THEY EAT BY THE WINDOW WITH GOOD VIEWS
This is nice.
- Where should we eat?
- Us?
Let's make it feel like a date.
- Maybe here?
- Should we eat here?
IN FRONT OF HUGE TOILET PAPER ROLL
Your hand's injured,
so let's just eat down here.
IN FRONT OF TV CABINET
- Shall we eat here?
- Yes, I'd like that.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE LIVING ROOM
- Bon appétit.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you for the food.
- It's good.
- It is? What a relief.
This is good. Zuha, it's delicious.
- It's good.
- It's okay?
It's delicious.
How old are you?
- We're the same age.
- We are?
- I was born in 2003.
- I was born in 2004.
Really?
You two look alike.
What about us looks the most similar?
Well…
It feels like two identical people
are looking at me.
Do you have any siblings?
- I'm an only child.
- Only child?
Let me be your sister.
That'd be an honor.
I hope we become good friends here.
- Nice to meet you.
- Jun-yeop and In-beom?
- Yes.
I was really curious
about your line of work.
We had a lot of guesses earlier.
An ascetic. A rocker.
- A rocker?
- Someone guessed a musician.
I'm just…
I'm just a college student.
- Just a college student?
- Yes.
What's your major?
Physical Education.
LEE IN-BEOM
MAJORING IN PE
What about you?
KIM JUN-YEOP
MAJORING IN AI
- AI?
- Yes.
Are you two
really close?
We went to the same kindergarten
when we were six.
And ever since,
we've attended the same schools.
- Really?
- We went to the same cram schools too.
- And so…
- Yeah?
We're supposed to enlist together too.
For real?
So we're checking out of here on March 3.
Right.
That's the day we enlist.
That's unbelievable.
But…
I hurt my hand last Monday.
Right.
So he's going to enter without me.
Really?
How did you hurt your hand?
Well…
While hitting a punching bag machine…
In an arcade?
Then, since you're enlisting soon,
did you grow out your hair on purpose?
- That's right.
- Seriously?
It must have taken years
to grow it out this long.
I started at the beginning of senior year.
You've grown it for two to three years?
Pretty much.
Do you use conditioner?
And you get hair treatments too?
What made you pick me?
Because you're an athlete too.
Then why didn't they pick me?
I'm not sure.
- It's different from normal rock climbing?
- Yes.
When you're rock climbing,
you use your bare hands,
- so you can feel everything.
- Right.
But we use ice axes and wear gloves.
So you need tools, not just hands.
Yes, we use tools.
It's ice climbing
that's been organized as a sport.
ORGANIZED AS COMPETITION ICE CLIMBING
So you're a professional?
It's more like a hobby for me.
And you came in second?
Yes.
Even if you sign a contract,
it's hard to earn enough
to make a living as a pro.
- Really?
- So you have to have another job.
I work on a mountain rescue team.
DAY JOB IS WITH MOUNTAIN RESCUE
Young-geon over there
is a full-time athlete.
He's currently the world champion.
So, including all the European climbers…
- The best?
- Yes, he's the best in the world.
- The world's top-ranked climber?
- Yes.
So, you're like Yeon-koung.
In a way, yes.
Then, are you on the national team?
Yes, all three of us are.
ICE CLIMBING NATIONAL TEAM MEMBERS
- Really?
- Yes.
Then, do you get any government funding
as part of the national team?
None whatsoever.
There's a reason why
the three of us are so close.
As a niche sport,
there aren't many places for us to train.
So, we rented a greenhouse
and built a wall inside it.
We made a space for training.
We go there in the evening
after getting off work.
So, you earn money
for competitions during the day.
Right.
Then, we train together in the evening.
- So, you do it because you love it.
- Yes.
- Out of passion.
- What can you do then?
- Sorry?
So as a climber,
what's the most ideal thing
you would like to see
happen in your sport?
- First, if it becomes an Olympic sport…
- Right.
If it becomes an Olympic sport in 2030…
And then, our country qualifies,
and if you win an Olympic medal?
- Yes. Then, all my dreams would come true.
- That would be amazing.
Seriously.
Let's go back down.
Just put your trays here.
Want to play a game?
I have an idea.
How about tag?
TAG ALL OF A SUDDEN?
Tag or hide-and-seek?
AT MEETING 3 HOURS AGO
How about hide-and-seek?
Hide-and-seek.
YES
THAT'S THE ONE
Is there anywhere to hide?
There aren't that many places to hide.
Yeah, it's so wide open.
Let's see how creative you all are.
Be creative.
Right, the time limit.
It's pretty spacious,
so let's take one minute to hide.
HIDING TIME IS 1 MINUTE
- Okay, let's play some hide-and-seek.
- Okay.
- We'll begin now.
MIN-CHEOL IS IT
There's really nowhere to hide.
JOON-KYU MOVES FAST
HE GOES FOR A PLACE OTHERS CAN'T REACH
BEHIND THE WEDDING DUCKS
Hey, I was going to hide there.
Would you like to go in?
No, you hide there.
I'll check how it looks for you.
You have to stand up.
- I should stand?
- I think you should.
Can you tell?
Okay, that's good.
It's not bad.
I've thought of where to hide.
YEON-KOUNG GOES UP AFTER CONCEDING HOODIE
SHE'S TAKING OUT THE TRASH?
AND GOES IN?
TOO SMALL
Damn it.
WHERE WILL SHE HIDE?
I should find somewhere new.
Gosh, I can't breathe.
THE BOSS HIDES UNDER THE COMFORTERS
HIDING TIME IS OVER
Here I come.
THE SEARCH BEGINS
I think someone's here.
ZUHA'S FOUND IN 10 SECONDS
You're it.
I picked a bad spot.
SEARCHING IN EARNEST
Young-geon.
No way.
He didn't climb up, did he?
Did he really climb up?
HE DID
Nice to see you.
THEY'RE FOUND ONE BY ONE
This is so obvious.
- I couldn't breathe.
- It's so hot.
- We're so bad at this.
- I know.
Who's left?
3 HAVEN'T BEEN FOUND YET
Where are they?
FOUND YOU
AFTER SHE FAILED TO HIDE IN THE TRASH BIN
SHE CHANGED PLANS
YEON-KOUNG'S NOT HERE
TAGS
Why did you come up here?
If I had more time,
I would've hidden better.
What a shame.
SHE STILL CLEANS UP AFTER HERSELF
Where are they?
- Where's Mr. Kian?
- Right?
Mr. Kian.
This is so stuffy.
Why hasn't he found me?
God, I can't breathe.
Come on.
HE WANTS TO BE FOUND SOON
He can't be here, can he?
STICKING OUT
THE BOSS IS FOUND
He's here.
Joon-kyu, come here and lie down.
EVERYONE KNOWS WHERE HE IS NOW
Goodness.
- Lie down properly on it.
- What are you doing?
Hey, come on!
GROANING
Did you find me? This is so tough.
Gosh, I can't breathe.
- Where's Jun-ho?
- He still hasn't found him yet?
- Where did he go?
- He hid so well.
JUN-HO'S HASN'T BEEN FOUND YET
A FOOT?
EARLIER
HE HID IN A T-SHIRT
TREMBLING
He's here.
Why aren't you tagging him?
It seems tough hiding there,
so I'm not tagging him.
HE CAN'T HEAR WELL
I can do this.
Where on earth is Jun-ho?
Where is he? The bathroom?
SLIPPING
Where did he go?
- Where did Jun-ho go?
- Where is he?
Where could he be?
How long does he have to do that for?
We can't find Jun-ho.
God. Geez.
Geez. You all knew, didn't you?
We had no idea where you were.
- That was impressive.
- You all knew.
I had no idea.
Gosh, I didn't know when to come down.
We only played one round, but we're done.
- I can't do it anymore.
- It's predictable now.
Exactly. It's over.
That was fun.
Goodness.
Are these two just college students?
Yes, they are,
and they're entering the military soon.
Really?
Speaking of which,
I wanted to ask Mr. Kian for a favor.
Okay.
Certain things are required.
Right.
Like shaving your head.
I brought hair clippers.
Seriously?
For real?
My enlistment's been pushed back a month,
but I can't let him do it alone.
You're shaving it too?
SHAVING HEADS TOGETHER
- Why?
- "Why?"
You'll regret it.
That's realistic advice.
For your friend?
Yes. I was supposed to do it anyway.
Think it over again,
and if you still want to shave it then…
Well, it's not my hair,
so you can if you want.
But you might regret it.
I won't.
A loyal friend.
KIAN'S B&B
Have a drink.
10:00 P.M.
LIGHTING PROVIDED TO SET THE MOOD
This is so romantic.
- This is perfect.
- Tonight's mood is so nice.
- Cheers.
Thank you. Welcome.
Did you sketch everything this time too?
Yes.
- It's like Gulliver's Travels.
- Right?
- It's like the theme.
- And there's me.
NODDING
I've never met
a woman taller than me.
"A woman taller than me."
- How tall are you?
- I'm 186 cm.
You're 186 cm? That's pretty short.
- "Pretty short"!
- "Short"!
In volleyball,
a lot of people are your height.
That's a cute height.
I'll call you my big sis.
Do I look gloomy to you, by any chance?
OUT OF THE BLUE?
- You look cheerful.
- The thing is…
One of the guests made… a claim?
- A complaint?
- Yes.
"Mr. Kian, you look so dark."
So when you arrived earlier,
I tried really hard.
- Really?
- Yes.
But you welcomed us so warmly.
To be honest, you're celebrities to us,
so there was a wall,
but I feel like that came down.
That's what we wanted.
You came all the way here,
so you should have fun.
And you're entering the military soon.
Right.
- You're going there right away?
- Yes.
Straight to our military unit.
- Really?
- What?
Right after checking out?
Straight to boot camp?
What about your parents?
I'm going to meet them there.
- That's insane.
- Really?
My goodness.
Did you say goodbye
to your friends already?
Yes, I did.
I was supposed to join him.
Gosh, you're going into the military?
Straight to the military from here?
FEELING SAD FOR SOME REASON
Hey, you guys come here.
Let's drink over here.
Where should we drink?
Could we borrow this room?
- Yes.
- Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Don't be so formal. Why are you kneeling?
- In-beom?
- Yes.
You two went to the same schools.
From kindergarten to high school.
- Including kindergarten too?
- Yes.
I've told him since middle school.
"We have to enlist
in the military together."
- So it was your idea.
- Yes.
But that's such a one-sided love.
Well, he does like me a lot.
And he's your best friend too?
Yes, he is.
- Is he the only one who thinks this?
- Not at all.
I also had such a friend
in elementary school.
Really?
You know, boys always have to decide
who their number one friend is.
- You know what I mean?
- I do.
He was my best friend back then.
- My favorite friend in the whole world.
- Right.
I had such a friend.
His name was Sang-gyeom.
It was always,
"My best friend, Sang-gyeom."
"Let's go to this middle school.
Let's go to high school together."
"Let's enter the military together."
I'd always say that.
EMPATHIZING
Then, you know how I feel.
Did you ever watch the show High Kick?
Kim Bum would always go over
to the main character's house.
I was the same way.
His mother would ask,
"Aren't you going to go home?"
And I'd say, "But I like it here."
- I liked hanging out with my friend.
- Right.
I go over to his house often too.
Then, he made another close friend later.
I was so jealous.
"He left me out
and became friends with someone else?"
I know how that feels.
When we first entered high school,
he'd try to become friends
with his new classmates.
And he'd have sleepovers at his house.
- And I was so hurt in middle school.
- Right.
He was so important to me
that I didn't make any other friends…
"You're my only friend,
but you're having fun with other kids?"
Right. Without him,
I'd have to just go home.
Yeah, and you have to
join the military together.
But you can't right now,
so it must be really frustrating for you.
It is.
You'll have to go through a lot
in the military anyway.
If you entered together,
that would've been a dream.
But your dream's been broken.
I was the same.
It was my dream to attend
the same high school as him.
But when it didn't happen,
it drove me crazy.
- And it's happening to you.
- Right.
It's like watching my young self.
Seriously?
All right.
Let's have a drink again tomorrow.
And we'll shave your hair.
What time is it?
It's 12:57 a.m. Almost 1:00 a.m.
- Did you finish talking?
- Yes.
Our 21-year-old friends…
They have a true friendship.
Yes, since kindergarten.
So they were supposed to enlist together,
but he can't with his hurt hand.
Isn't this such a beautiful story?
Just have a drink,
and stop talking nonsense.
JUMPS UP AGAIN
As soon as In-beom checks out later on…
REPEATING HIMSELF
…he's going straight to the military.
How many times are you going to say that?
This is something
I need to say over and over again.
We can't forget it.
- We didn't forget.
- I will…
I'll tell you this again tomorrow,
so prepare yourselves.
WHILE THEY TALK AND LAUGH
IT STARTS TO QUIETLY SNOW
It's snowing.
- It's snowing hard.
- It's snowing right now.
It's snowing, Boss.
It is.
It hadn't snowed until now.
- Let's have a snowball fight tomorrow.
- Yes.
And we should make a snowman.
Yes, a snowman.
But it's snowing a lot.
A BIT INTENSE
It's not good if we can't go out tomorrow.
Right, that can't happen.
Let's just put this to the side.
THEY WRAP UP
AND GO TO THEIR RESPECTIVE BEDS
Min-cheol might snore a lot.
MIN-CHEOL, YOUNG-GEON: FRIDGE
We better sleep now.
A-JIN, A-RIN: TV CABINET
JUN-YEOP, IN-BEOM, JOON-KYU: LIVING ROOM
- Sleep tight, Boss.
- Good night.
Good night.
HANGERS
I mean, that's some pretty heavy snowfall.
THE SNOW SUDDENLY GETS HEAVIER
There was a heavy-snow alert.
HEAVY SNOW EXPECTED OVERNIGHT IN GANGWON
What if we can't open the door tomorrow?
THE SNOW SLOWLY FALLS EVEN HARDER
DAY 7
KIAN'S B&B
IT'S BEEN SNOWING FOR 7 HOURS
8:00 A.M.
How many times have you used the sauna?
The sauna? A lot of times.
Almost every day.
People used it if they wanted to.
ZUHA, A-JIN, AND A-RIN HAVE A MORNING CHAT
Let's pack the equipment.
- Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
How long does it take to get there?
About two hours.
- Two hours?
- Yes.
Then, it's a four-hour round trip?
If we don't go climb the ice walls now…
- Now's the only time?
- Exactly.
Can I take a look, Min-cheol?
So you wear gloves
and stick these into the ice to climb up?
Yes, that's for speed.
- For speed climbing?
- Yes.
Gosh, it's pretty big.
The tools are all…
Gosh, this is no joke.
I wish we had these here.
It's so hard to climb that.
Don't your feet hurt?
Give it a try.
I guess you do it like this.
- Right?
- That's right.
- Like this?
- Yes.
That's it.
- Like this?
- Yes.
This is better.
INTRIGUED
YEON-KOUNG SLEPT IN
AFTER ALSO SLEEPING IN, THE BOSS GETS UP
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
Yes.
Boss is here.
You look clean. You washed up.
Yes, I took a shower.
SATISFIED
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, very well.
Did you sleep well, Boss?
I feel like my body's broken.
I feel so worn out.
- It's a battle of stamina.
- This is a workout.
We'll open that later in the evening.
- The jacuzzi.
- Tonight? That's good.
Everyone, have a safe trip.
Will they be okay with the snow?
I don't think it'll stop soon.
The snow is no joke outside.
THE PATH IS COVERED IN SNOW
SO ARE THE GUESTS' CARS
THEY DECIDE TO HEAD OUT
Where are you going, Jun-ho?
I'll go clear the snow off their car
and apply some liquid tire chain.
I'll be back.
HE GOES TO STORAGE
TO GET SNOW REMOVAL TOOLS
This should do.
This is no joke.
It snowed so much.
It's unbelievable.
I can't believe how the scenery
just changed like this.
See you later.
- See you.
- How many days left until the military?
I'm going tomorrow.
You're entering tomorrow?
Yes.
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
- I'll get going.
- Okay.
- You're not cold, Jun-yeop?
- No.
I'm okay now, so…
But it'll get cold later. Put mine on.
You're going to wear that
in Daegwallyeong in February?
Thank you.
- We'll get going.
- See you.
WARM IN THE BOSS'S JACKET AS HE HEADS OUT
It really wasn't me.
Which one's your car?
This one.
HE REMOVES SNOW FROM THE GUEST'S CARS
This is no joke.
It should be okay
if you turn the wipers on.
A-JIN AND A-RIN'S CAR TOO
Your hand must be cold.
Thank you.
- Have a safe trip.
- We will.
WHILE JUN-HO TENDS TO THE GUESTS
We need to shovel the snow.
What's going on?
What happened overnight?
I should put on gloves.
TODAY'S ADDITIONAL TASK
SNOW REMOVAL
We can't even sweep
this lumpy snow though.
Still, clearing snow is our job.
My gosh.
ZUHA ALSO STARTS
I'll sweep some away first,
and you push it aside.
Okay.
JUST FOLLOW ME
LIGHT BRUSHING
It'll take all day if you do it like that.
Harder.
Sweep back and forth like this.
HARDER?
Harder.
LIGHTLY
PAUSING
Zuha, you're not working hard today.
I was watching how you did it.
You go to the front.
You're sweeping what I already swept.
Busted.
Longer strokes. All the way.
And go forward.
That's it.
Good.
You're doing well.
Go.
- We have to sweep the whole path.
- All of it?
- The whole path.
- Seriously?
THEY HAVE TO SWEEP THE WHOLE PATH
We can't have them
slip on their way back.
- Understand?
- Yes.
Where did Boss go?
THE BOSS IS…
This is hopeless.
SHOVELING
UNCOVERS MAT THAT HAD VANISHED
CLEARING PATH, CLEARING ENTRANCE
Damn it. Is it frozen? What's with this?
THE MAT IS SAVED
Great job.
You're doing great.
- Hurry and join us.
- Okay.
It must've been tough.
RETURNS AFTER SEEING GUESTS OFF
I should go and clear that path.
JUN-HO CLEARS ANOTHER PATH
FROZEN SOLID
THE BOSS STARTS CLEARING
ONE END OF THE PATH
I'm so tired.
Gosh, this is…
DIGGING
It won't break loose.
LOOKING AROUND
It keeps snowing.
SNOWING HEAVILY
PILING UP AGAIN
Hey, this is endless.
It's endless.
It keeps snowing.
Yeon-koung!
- Stop!
- Stop?
I should go all the way.
It keeps snowing.
Still, it's better to clear it,
so their feet won't sink in.
I'll go all the way to the end.
- All the way?
- Yes.
We might as well do it now.
All right.
When they come back later,
it won't be slippery.
WE HAVE TO DO THIS THEN
We should clear as much as we can.
Geez, Boss. This is too tough.
Hang in there. We're almost done.
My hands are so cold.
You got the hang of it now. Yes, Zuha.
Yes, push and sweep. There you go!
Good. You got much better, Zuha.
THE PATH IS ALL CLEARED
All the way.
ZUHA WORKS HARD UNTIL THE END
Take a seat.
GROANING
It looks so cool. Look over there.
- Nice, right?
- Yes.
As the snow falls over you,
you don't get to experience
something like this often.
Yes, you're right.
It's really rare.
The way I see it,
it'll pile up again.
Don't say that.
- Still, it's better than before.
- It is.
- It's flat now.
- Right.
Kian's B&B is all about stamina.
Most people wouldn't be able to handle it.
They would fall sick.
Let's go.
- We're going?
- We should go back.
- Now?
- Let's go.
Let's sweep as we go.
Yeon-koung, that's enough.
Let's go sledding.
- I want to ride.
- I'll bring them over.
Here they are.
A SACK FOR THE BOSS
AND SLEDS FOR EMPLOYEES
GRINNING WIDELY
Isn't this course too advanced?
STEEPER THAN EXPECTED
I should get a sled too.
HE GOES TO GET A SLED TOO
You're really going?
- This is a piece of cake.
- Yeah.
I'll go first.
JUN-HO GOES FIRST
Here I go!
How is it?
STAGGERS
Is it fun?
- It is fun.
- Really?
It's so fast. Be careful here.
A BIT NERVOUS
- Are you going?
- Of course.
WAIT FOR ME
- Is it fun?
- He says it is.
Come on down. I'll catch you.
How far are you going?
It's no joke! Hey, it's no joke.
- I underestimated it, Jun-ho.
- You can get off.
It's no joke!
Be careful.
It's faster than you think.
GOES EVEN FASTER
ZUHA IS FLYING
- You were flying since you're light.
- Right, you were so fast.
Hey, don't catch me.
Don't catch you?
No. Here I go!
AIRBORNE
HIGH SPEED
- He's so fast.
- That's it.
Move out of the way!
Move out of the way.
Hey, this is fun!
SO THRILLING
LET'S DO IT AGAIN!
I'm pretty sure poop
is everywhere around here.
You're right.
- He's fast.
- He's so fast.
This is no joke. Come on!
I bumped into that.
I think you can't pull so hard.
- Don't pull? Okay.
- If you do, you'll stop.
TRYING AGAIN
Okay, it's this feeling!
I like this feeling.
A SLED FULL OF HAPPINESS
This is removing the snow automatically.
I can't see anything.
THEY ALL LOOK LIKE A MESS
Want to make a snowman?
- A snowman?
- Yeah, the snow sticks so well.
THE SNOWMAN WAS A LIE
The snow hurts a bit.
THEY MOVE INTO BATTLE FORMATION
Jun-ho, thanks for your work.
A SNOWBALL OF LOVE?
- Yeon-koung.
- What?
DELIVERS A SNOWBALL OF LOVE
I love you!
BLOCKS THE LOVE
What on earth?
RIGHT, SHE WAS A VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
Hey, let's count to three
and throw it at a person of your choice.
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, right?
ONLY ONE WHO DOESN'T KNOW
- Okay. One…
- Two…
Three!
FIGHTING BACK
DEADLOCKED
Hey!
You fooled me into coming here. Come here!
RUNNING AWAY
She and I wrestled a bit,
but she didn't punch me or anything.
She's kind-hearted.
KIND-HEARTED FRIEND
I'm so exhausted.
This is insane.
Gosh, that was so damn funny.
- I'm hungry now.
- What?
- We should go eat.
- Right.
SO BUSY PLAYING THEY FORGOT TO EAT
Is there anything to eat?
Let's go in and see.
Maybe we shouldn't have used up
our energy before cleaning.
I should wash up.
I am so spent.
Gosh, I feel so cold.
- Are you cold?
- I am.
This is so nice.
WARM
- Yeon-koung.
- Yes?
You know, if more guests come,
could you give your room to them?
Sure. Let's move out of our rooms.
Okay.
- Let's just sleep here.
- Okay.
- Hey, warm yourself up.
- Yeah, I should.
I feel sleepy now.
SLEEPY
What do we eat?
Let's order in today.
Yeah, let's order something.
LOOKING AT A DELIVERY APP
- Order what you want to eat.
- Yeah.
SHE CHOOSES KOREAN FOOD
I'll have pork backbone soup.
This is what Zuha chose? Hangover soup?
SO HAPPY CHOOSING WHAT TO EAT
Hey. I'm sorry to say this, but…
I have bad news.
It says, "Due to inclement weather
caused by snow, delivery is unavailable."
A DEVASTATING
SURPRISE
EVEN THE DOOR FLIES OPEN
We said
we should've ordered in yesterday!
Let us get delivery.
We told you yesterday.
We told you yesterday!
I told you we should order in yesterday!
Everyone.
Embracing the unpredictable
is the joy of life.
Ramyeon again?
One, two, three.
I'll cook something up quickly.
Leave it to me.
WASHES RICE
PUTS IN CHOPPED VEGETABLES
GOCHUJANG
SESAME OIL
A LOT OF CHEESE
RAMYEON SOUP POWDER FOR EXTRA FLAVOR
ADDS PROTEIN TOO
- Is it a stew?
- Yeah.
PRESUMABLY SOME KIND OF THICK STEW
NATURALLY SITS
IN FRONT OF SINK WITH DISHES
We didn't do them,
- so there's a lot from yesterday.
- Right.
Geez, how many times have we washed these?
- Gosh, my back.
- Goodness.
Gosh, my back!
Goodness!
I feel like we're always
cleaning this darn house.
CLEANING DOWNSTAIRS
Our chores keep piling up.
FOLDING LAUNDRY
TIRED
Done.
All done. Let's eat.
- Let's eat!
- Okay.
What did you make?
It's a stew.
- A stew again?
- Yes.
But you said
you'd make something delicious.
I can't make anything else.
What's wrong with you?
Just come try it.
TRYING IT FIRST
It's good. Come and try it.
Hurry up, or you won't get any food.
- Coming!
- Coming.
I have to wrap this up first, sir.
Do it after lunch.
I'm dying over here.
I want double the pay.
- Boss.
- Yes?
Give us a bonus.
Where's the kimchi?
KIMCHI INSTEAD OF BONUSES
A stew again? Geez.
It's always either a stew or ramyeon.
I put in rice instead of noodles.
This rotten…
I should just quit.
Try it.
Good work, everyone.
Thank you.
Let's eat this and…
12:50 P.M.
It's spicy. Will you be okay, Zuha?
- How spicy?
- Pretty spicy.
Pretty spicy?
Try it.
Thank you for the food.
"Thank you for the food."
I'll just use my spoon
instead of chopsticks.
- Sure.
- Don't use chopsticks.
Don't use them.
There'll be more things to wash.
USING CHOPSTICKS IS A WASTE
I bit the bullet
and gave you bowls to use too.
It's delicious.
That's all that matters then.
I feel like we've become farmers.
Clearing snow outside
and cleaning inside.
Seriously.
POT IS ALREADY ALMOST EMPTY
You worked so much
that you're scraping the pot.
We should eat the scorched rice too.
- Hey, Zuha.
- That's coal.
- The bottom's no good.
- Eat the top.
- The upper part.
- It's almost coal.
I can't tell you to eat that.
I'll just eat it.
She's not shying away.
She's not shying away now.
Honestly,
someone has to come now.
Who?
Anyone who'll help us.
I seriously hope someone comes to help.
Your phone's ringing.
- Where's it?
- Over there.
Be careful.
Where is it?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hello.
- I'm checking in today.
- Yes.
How many are in your party?
- It's just me.
- Just you?
Then, please come
to the address we'll send you.
1 GUEST IS EXPECTED TO CHECK IN
How many?
- One. It's a woman.
- One.
- I'll wrap up down here.
- Okay.
BACK TO WORK
- Another guest?
- Hello?
Hello?
We're three high schoolers
checking in to Kian's B&B today.
I see. Hello.
High schoolers.
- Three?
- Yes.
What time can we check in?
You can come at 4:00 p.m.
I'll send you the address.
Okay, thank you. Bye.
Bye.
- It's all on my hair.
- I didn't expect this much.
3 MORE GUESTS TO CHECK IN
There are already four more guests now.
I told you it'd be four more.
Did you prepare the rice?
THEY START PREPARING RICE FOR DINNER FIRST
We're out of water.
I have to go get another bottle.
I should throw out the recyclables.
THROWING OUT RECYCLABLES
BEFORE GUESTS COME
Zuha, could you bring
just these two outside?
STILL SNOWING HEAVILY
It's so cold.
Gosh, my feet are so cold.
My goodness.
- Zuha, can you carry this?
- Sorry?
THIS
Yes.
One, two, three.
STRONG ZUHA
IS OUT OF STRENGTH
It's like the Arctic here.
Gosh, hold on!
The wind is so strong.
- Give it to me.
- Where do I put it?
- I'll just…
- Yeah, there.
Are you working her hard
because she's the youngest?
Well, we did it together.
Goodness. Our youngest is working so hard.
- Lift it up?
- Yeah, hold on.
THE BOSS WILL MOVE THE WATER UP
Can you do it with one hand?
I don't think it'll work.
Wait. Hold on.
RETREATS
Can you take this up?
- Push it all the way up.
- Put it on your head.
Push it up all the way. Wait.
If you drop it…
JUN-HO CARRIES IT UP
We did it.
PANTING
We're done.
But there's nothing to drink.
- Something to drink?
- Yes.
- Drink this.
- Okay.
Jun-ho, want some coffee?
- Canned coffee?
- Yes, please.
Throw it up.
TOOT
LETS OUT GAS
PLOPS DOWN
OUT OF BREATH
Did you hear that?
My goodness. I'm so embarrassed.
I didn't want you to see
that weak side of me.
DRIVING THE SMELL AWAY
I must've been too exhausted to hold it.
- Did you fart?
- What?
- He farted.
Again?
It sounded like something came out.
Are you okay?
Nothing came out.
What do you mean "something came out"?
I have class, you know.
Gosh, you should fart often for her.
It's been a while
since she laughed like that.
Tell me if you feel down, and I'll fart.
Damn it.
I WANT TO HIDE
Geez.
It's so embarrassing
the more I think about it.
SO EMBARRASSED
What are you laughing about?
Are you laughing about that?
IT MAKES HER LAUGH
I don't think I'll ever forget it.
Hurry up and forget it.
Again?
- No more.
- Please, no more.
Hello?
We made a reservation for two people.
I see. Hello.
What's the address?
I'll text you the address.
- Okay, then.
- Okay, bye.
How many do we have in total then?
Five men and two women,
so that's seven.
Seven plus six.
- That's 13 guests in total.
- What?
Including us, that's 17 people.
LARGEST NUMBER OF PEOPLE SO FAR
- Gosh, it's a lot.
- Thirteen people?
Where do we sleep, Zuha?
YONGSO ICE PARK
MIN-CHEOL, YOUNG-GEON, JOON-KYU
Today's a good day to climb.
YONGSO ICE PARK
A perfect day to train.
THE TEAM IS HERE TO PRACTICE ICE CLIMBING
THE WALL IS COVERED IN ICE
THEY PRACTICE CLIMBING UP
TO THE DESTINATION POINT
Where are you going to climb?
Maybe there?
It's about 24 m high.
- Shall we give it a try?
- Go ahead.
WORLD CHAMPION YOUNG-GEON STARTS HIS CLIMB
You have to use ice axes
and wear crampons on your shoes.
SWING
THE ACT OF STRIKING AN ICE AXE INTO ICE
KICK
THE ACT OF DRIVING CRAMPONS INTO ICE
He's good.
HE CLIMBS AS HE SWINGS AND KICKS
You're looking good.
- Finished.
YOUNG-GEON'S FINISHED
THE YOUNGEST JOON-KYU STARTS HIS CLIMB
All I know is, this is just fun.
THE OLDEST MIN-CHEOL STARTS HIS CLIMB
He's going smoothly.
Finished!
TRAINING ENDS
Gosh, the season's really over now.
CAFE IN DAEGWALLYEONG
A-JIN, A-RIN
Or making cheese. I think that's good too.
Me too.
- Should we go make cheese together?
- Okay.
WHO IS A-RIN CALLING?
- Hello?
Where are you going next?
We're going up in the cable car right now.
- Cable car?
- Yes.
If you have no plans after,
want to join us?
- Okay.
- Really?
Sounds good.
THE FOUR MEET
AT A CHEESE EXPERIENCE CENTER
So you like dating shows.
Let's pretend this is a dating show.
SUGGESTS DATING SHOW ROLEPLAY
IT'LL BE SO FUN
My arm hurts.
I'll do it.
You're so good!
GLANCING
Which one is the flower?
It looks pretty.
It's pretty like someone I know.
Watch me, babe.
I feel hot.
And dip it again.
One, two.
We have good teamwork
TIME LEFT UNTIL ENLISTMENT
I better start cooking.
2:45 P.M.
TODAY'S MAIN CHEF IS JUN-HO
TODAY'S DISH 1
POTATO JEON
That's 13 guests in total.
We might have to sleep
in the kitchen at this rate.
TONIGHT'S DINNER IS FOR 17 PEOPLE?
HE STARTS TO PREPARE 17 SERVINGS
NEATLY
THE CHOPPING FACTORY IS RUNNING
ENDLESS JULIENNING
ADDS POTATO STARCH
SALT
THE POTATO JEON BATTER IS READY
Jun-ho, do you need our help?
Come cook the potato jeon for me.
I'll come up. Hey, Zuha.
- Yes?
- Do I look better with glasses on or off?
GLASSES ON
This is me with glasses on.
GLASSES OFF
- Which one?
- I like you with glasses on.
PUFFS OUT CHEEKS
Better with them on?
Why did you puff out your cheeks?
That's the cutest expression for me.
The cutest expression I can make.
That's why.
Is it potato and tuna?
Isn't it Spam?
It might be so.
But don't you think
it won't come together?
IT WON'T COME TOGETHER?
It's not binding together.
YEON-KOUNG TRIES
You're right. We can't flip it.
IMPOSSIBLE TO FLIP IT
This won't do.
I don't think he put in
a lot of potato starch.
Right?
THE POTATO JEON BATTER IS READY
- He should've put in more.
- Starch?
What do we do?
Let's go with potato stir-fry.
TODAY'S DISH 1
POTATO STIR-FRY
Jun-ho, we can't make jeon with this.
- So we decided to make it a stir-fry.
- Okay.
MAIN CHEF APPROVES
Are we done?
I should do the dishes too.
It's hard to scrub these.
Seriously.
GLANCING
I'm doing all the work, Zuha.
- I'm working too.
- All the work.
I'm working too.
I'm doing all the dishes.
No, I was about to do it.
I always do this.
MAIN CHEF JUN-HO'S NEXT DISH
TODAY'S DISH 2
KIMCHI JJIGAE
CHECKING THE RECIPE
ADDS CHILI POWDER
SOUP SOY SAUCE
MINCED GARLIC
TUNA FISH SAUCE
SIMMERING
SATISFIED
THE KIMCHI JJIGAE IS READY
All finished. Right?
THEY FINISH DISHWASHING TOO
FLOPS DOWN
SLIDING OUT
Let's give it a try now.
THE BOSS IS UP TO SOMETHING
Hey, wait.
Can I take a photo of you?
HE PLANS TO DRAW THE STAFF
THE ONE IN THE PHOTO IS ASLEEP
A SKETCH IS DONE IN NO TIME
A BEER BOX PALETTE
HESITANT
ONLY 5 WATERCOLORS
RED-NOSED YEON-KOUNG
SHOCKED
PAINTS RED ALL OVER HER FACE
CONFUSED
DRAWING HER EYES, NOSE, AND MOUTH
LIGHT AND SHADING NEXT
Why does it look so scary?
WHAT?
Wait, that's me.
What?
Wait. That's me.
Gosh, you draw so well.
He's so good.
So you really are a cartoonist.
Make me look a bit prettier.
Prettier?
Got it. I'll make it more beautiful.
- Is that Yeon-koung?
- Yeah.
IMPRESSED
So we're getting to see you
do your day job?
My day job? I feel embarrassed.
That's good enough, right?
PLOPS DOWN
I'm so tired.
I can only draw one per day.
- Weren't you drawing for almost two hours?
- Yeah.
I should make it brighter.
The face looks so dark.
It shows the theme
of Kian's B&B this season.
What theme?
THE THEME OF KIAN'S B&B?
Darkness.
No way. No, it has to be bright.
I mean, Smita said you looked dark,
and it shows in the drawings.
Very dark.
No way. Smita will…
If Smita sees this,
she'll be pissed about how gloomy it is.
THE SINGING BOWL
THAT GUEST JUN-HO GAVE HIM
GO AWAY, DARKNESS
KEEP GOING, KIAN'S B&B 2
When will they come?
I wonder if they can open it.
3:50 P.M.
SNOWFALL IS SLOWLY GETTING HARSHER
It's so white outside.
I want to take a photo too.
THEY ARRIVE WHILE WATCHING THE SNOW
Let's go.
- Thank you.
The scenery is amazing.
Thank you.
- Hello. Are you guests?
- Hello.
- Yes, we are.
- Yes. Hello.
- Checking in today?
- Yes.
- I'm checking in today too.
This looks so romantic.
This is incredible.
Gosh, my shoes are now…
They're all soaked now.
- My socks are all wet.
- It can't be helped.
SNOW PILED UP AGAIN AFTER BEING CLEARED
Getting there is already an ordeal.
BIZARRE CHAOS ON THE PATH
Why is the door so big?
What is this?
They're here.
- We'll prepare the welcome party.
- Right.
- Hey, this--
- Just a moment.
- Okay. Hello.
- Hello.
AMAZED
Kian, we have to make welcome drinks.
How much?
ENDLESS POURING OF LEMON JUICE
Tell me when to stop.
- Stop.
- This much?
Should we add a bit more?
- Add some more.
- More?
AS MUCH AS THEY'RE WELCOMED
WELCOME DRINKS ARE READY
PUTTING ON SOCKS
READY WITH HER VOLLEYBALL
Should I do this? Okay, I'll change it.
EVERYONE
GOES
TO THEIR POSITIONS
BRIEF SINGING PRACTICE
- I'll open it.
- Okay.
CLANK
It's opening.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you!
- Nice to meet you!
- Hello.
Nice to meet you!
- Good to see you.
- What is this?
Welcome!
Here are our employees
Employees!
Hello!
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome.
Here. Your hands are freezing.
You must be so cold.
- Your welcome drinks.
- Thank you.
You're the high schoolers?
Yes, we are.
Welcome.
Awkward, right?
BUSTED
THEN, WE'LL WELCOME YOU MORE PASSIONATELY
- Welcome.
WELCOME DANCE
NEW GUESTS APPROACH
HE HEARS THE SOUND
Can you hide there for a bit?
Over there.
ASSIGNED SPOT FOR GUESTS
DURING WELCOMING
This is fun.
CLANK
Welcome!
We were waiting!
- Hello.
- Come on in
- You've come a long way.
Yes, this is Kian's B&B.
Welcome!
AUTOMATIC RESPONSE
Our youngest employee.
- Kazuha!
- Hello.
SURPRISED
Geez, this is the last time.
Hello.
Yeon-koung
Would you like to receive this?
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Yo, Jun-ho.
Hello.
Thank you.
And here are the other guests
you'll stay with!
HERE ARE THE OTHER GUESTS
That's so cute.
- Hello.
- So adorable.
HESITANT
- They came today too.
- They came today.
I see. Hello.
Please, come on in.
Gosh, you got snowed on a lot.
It's cold outside, isn't it?
6 GUESTS HAVE CHECKED IN
All right.
Let me give you an introduction.
Everyone, in life,
I'm sure you'll get to stay
in many big hotels and accommodations.
But you'll never get to stay
in a bigger room
than this!
QUIET CHEER
Here, you can comfortably
think of us as close friends
and stay with…
QUIET CHEER
This is nice.
Gosh, this is hard.
- You're staying for three days?
- Yes.
THEY'LL ALL STAY FOR THREE DAYS
So they're staying until the last day.
IN THAT CASE
- Zuha, let's move out of our rooms.
- Right.
YEON-KOUNG AND ZUHA VACATE THEIR ROOMS
- You have a lot of stuff.
- Yes.
Goodbye, my beloved bed.
I'm leaving.
RAMYEON BOXES ARE EMPTIED
You can first decide where you'll stay.
The three of us
will use the ramyeon boxes.
THEY CHOOSE THE RAMYEON BOXES
We'll take the sofa.
THEY CHOOSE THE SOFA
What are your names?
- I'm Jang Seo-young.
- Seo-young.
- I'm Kim Han-na.
- Han-na.
What's your name?
I'm Lee Su-ryeon.
- Lee Su-ryeon?
- Yes.
I'm Lee Seong-bhin.
I'm Sim Hyeon-seo.
I'm Choo Yun-woo.
Can I call you Jun-ho?
Of course, as you please.
I'm old enough to be your uncle.
I checked when you debuted. Was it 2008?
Yes. When were you born again?
In 2009.
SHOCKED
You made your debut
a year before I was born.
Really?
Nice to meet you.
You can still call me by my name.
I'm fine with it.
I'll call you Jun-ho.
I'd be thankful for that.
Which high school do you go to?
Gyeongnam Science High School.
- A science high school?
- Yes.
You guys are smart.
STEPS BACK
Where do you want to go to college?
SNU's School of Earth
and Environmental Sciences.
- Earth and Environmental Sciences?
- Yes.
- And you?
- I want to major in astrophysics.
Astrophysics?
They're similar.
Earth science and astrophysics.
We're members of the astronomy club.
- The same club.
- The astronomy club?
Yes, so all our stuff over there
are the telescopes we brought.
Telescopes?
A total lunar eclipse
will take place tomorrow.
- A total lunar eclipse tomorrow?
- Yes.
Then, which one will be covered?
The moon or the sun?
It's a lunar eclipse.
And "lunar" means "moon," right?
It happens
when the Earth's shadow covers the moon.
So, they overlap?
Yes.
One of the characteristics
is that the moon looks red.
THE THREE CAME TO DAEGWALLYEONG
TO OBSERVE STARS
The moon will be slowly covered…
Will we be able to see it?
It's snowing,
so will it be visible tomorrow?
We should check the forecast.
Please take a seat.
Some adorable guests have come.
And all three of you are wearing glasses.
- Right?
- They go to Gyeongnam Science High School.
STARING
You look like Ddochi.
- Ddochi?
- Ddochi.
- You know Ddochi? No?
- I don't.
Ddochi. It's a very cute character.
- I look like it?
- Yeah.
HE'S ADORABLE
What made you decide to come alone?
I like traveling by myself.
I see. You usually like traveling alone.
Then, what's your major?
I'm a nursing major.
LEE SU-RYEON
NURSING STUDENT
STARING AGAIN
You look a bit like Ji Ye-eun.
"Control yourself."
You really do look a bit like Ye-eun.
I get that a lot.
For a moment,
I thought I was back in Ulleungdo Island.
IS THIS ULLEUNGDO ISLAND?
AT THAT MOMENT
A CAR APPROACHES KIAN'S B&B
I'm so curious to see what it looks like.
I can't wait.
ANOTHER GUEST?
What on earth do they do here?
WHO IS IN THIS SUSPICIOUS CAR?
Goodness.
DEX HAS COME TO KIAN'S B&B
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu